[{"answer": "I think people don't really -- it's hard for people to grasp the -- everything that happened.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 47, "question": "And the gap between those two positions in the public estimation, I guess in your own estimation is just so massive, isn't it?", "qSentId": 46}, {"answer": "No, they're not aware.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "So -- I mean even now are they aware of what happened to you?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "ONES: Incredibly.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 115, "question": "How intoxicating is that?", "qSentId": 114}, {"answer": "Right.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 123, "question": "Because you didn't want to hear it?", "qSentId": 122}, {"answer": "Yes, I mean, but even -- even before then, at the age of 15, I made my first Olympic team, you know.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 131, "question": "Twenty-three?", "qSentId": 130}, {"answer": "-- it's -- it's the reality check --", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 138, "question": "You know?", "qSentId": 137}, {"answer": "Well, I -- I -- I realized that -- that my priorities were totally out of whack and that -- that I had to figure out who I was, not Marion Jones, the superstar athlete, the pretty smile, the charm and all that.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 145, "question": "What did you learn about yourself?", "qSentId": 144}, {"answer": "It was.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 172, "question": "Appalling painful though it is, that's the beginning of the moving on process, isn't it?", "qSentId": 171}, {"answer": "Oh, extremely painful, because, you know, she was and still is my biggest support.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 194, "question": "-- and look her in the eye and say, it's true?", "qSentId": 193}, {"answer": "Not too long after I -- after I pled guilty.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 198, "question": "Did you turn to her, having rejected her in the way that you said you did -- what was the moment you turned back to her?", "qSentId": 197}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 203, "question": "Because your mother, I guess, had lived the great highs?", "qSentId": 202}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 217, "question": "Was she angry with you?", "qSentId": 216}, {"answer": "Well, certainly my decision in men.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 222, "question": "What was the poorest choice your mother thinks you ever made?", "qSentId": 221}, {"answer": "I don't know, I think I saw -- I saw something in them that perhaps I was lacking in my childhood.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 231, "question": "Why were you attracted to the bad guys?", "qSentId": 230}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 235, "question": "Do you have any relationship with him at all?", "qSentId": 234}, {"answer": "Possibly.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 238, "question": "So you -- you were craving a kind of father substitute, possibly?", "qSentId": 237}, {"answer": "No, he's passed.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 242, "question": "Is he still alive, your biological father?", "qSentId": 241}, {"answer": "I did.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 245, "question": "Did you have any feelings about that when you heard?", "qSentId": 244}, {"answer": "ONES: No.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 255, "question": "Not -- but not having a strong male presence in your life and all the pressure on your mom to bring you up and everything, it can't help, can it?", "qSentId": 254}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 262, "question": "I mean it's like a shark pool, isn't it?", "qSentId": 261}, {"answer": "Let's take another break.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 272, "question": "But by the time the child is old enough and go off to college, how much protecting can you do?", "qSentId": 271}, {"answer": "We can get there reasonably quick.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 277, "question": "Can we get there quick, please?", "qSentId": 276}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 289, "question": "And you'd gone from 80,000 dollars a race?", "qSentId": 288}, {"answer": "Correct.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 306, "question": "Your kids went to stay with your family in Barbados, right?", "qSentId": 305}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 321, "question": "Would you have still won the gold?", "qSentId": 320}, {"answer": "Sure.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 335, "question": "Can I play Devil's Advocate with you?", "qSentId": 334}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 344, "question": "Is that the honest truth?", "qSentId": 343}, {"answer": "Well, I didn't -- it -- it was tough to hand back the medals, certainly.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 363, "question": "That moment, when you hand back the medals and you hear this guy say that about you and that is how you're being branded to America, how did that make you feel?", "qSentId": 362}, {"answer": "No, not at all.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 372, "question": "-- what might have been?", "qSentId": 371}, {"answer": "-- keeping it secret or is tempted to or believes it's the only way they can win a gold medal --", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 383, "question": "Or is tempted?", "qSentId": 382}, {"answer": "First of all, think about the consequences of your choices.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 386, "question": "-- there's nobody better to ask, what -- what advice would you give them?", "qSentId": 385}, {"answer": "Well, we miss him.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 425, "question": "How does it feel for you going back on tour, on the road and Michael's no longer here?", "qSentId": 424}, {"answer": "Well, I agree with Marlon with what he was saying.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 439, "question": "And Tito, how do you feel?", "qSentId": 438}, {"answer": "Six shows a day.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 448, "question": "Six shows a day?", "qSentId": 447}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 450, "question": "Is that right?", "qSentId": 449}, {"answer": "Well, that's a very good point.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 463, "question": "See what is abnormal?", "qSentId": 462}, {"answer": "I get it totally.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 487, "question": "Or do you now -- now that you are older and you have had kids, some of you yourselves, do you get it?", "qSentId": 486}, {"answer": "I'm the oldest.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 498, "question": "When you say that -- as you sit here now, you're all in your late 50s, 60 in one -- you are the oldest right?", "qSentId": 497}, {"answer": "Sixty one.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 501, "question": "How old are you, 60, 61?", "qSentId": 500}, {"answer": "Very well.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 519, "question": "How do you get along with him now?", "qSentId": 518}, {"answer": "We had worries about just -- later during the circle of people, but not so much of what he was achieving.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 572, "question": "Did you worry that it was too much for one person to take?", "qSentId": 571}, {"answer": "Well, I was wondering how he was going to do 50 dates, first of all.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 579, "question": "I mean, how did you feel as brothers?", "qSentId": 578}, {"answer": "I thought he was fine, yeah.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 584, "question": "Did you feel he was OK and himself?", "qSentId": 583}, {"answer": "Well, I feel that -- like we're supposed to have forgiving hearts.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 591, "question": "What do you feel, Tito, about Conrad Murray?", "qSentId": 590}, {"answer": "Sure, I forgive him.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 595, "question": "Do you forgive him?", "qSentId": 594}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 598, "question": "Do you all feel that way?", "qSentId": 597}, {"answer": "No, I don't feel that way at all.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 600, "question": "You don't, Jermaine?", "qSentId": 599}, {"answer": "I feel like it's just negligence and not on his -- it's on his part plus others.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 602, "question": "What do you feel?", "qSentId": 601}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 643, "question": "The accusations, The molestation charge, all that kind of thing, did it have a very bad impact on him, do you think?", "qSentId": 642}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 666, "question": "\"Shake Your Body\"?", "qSentId": 665}, {"answer": "Of course.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 687, "question": "Do you ever have arguments?", "qSentId": 686}, {"answer": "I would.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 696, "question": "Who would win if you were to fight?", "qSentId": 695}, {"answer": "I like the old stuff, like \"I Want You Back\" and \"ABC,\" \"The Love You Save,\" the Motown stuff.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 702, "question": "Tito?", "qSentId": 701}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 718, "question": "Really?", "qSentId": 717}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 724, "question": "All the hits?", "qSentId": 723}, {"answer": "I don't think you really can.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 732, "question": "How are you going to commemorate Michael on tour, in terms of the actual tour, do you think?", "qSentId": 731}, {"answer": "Here's what happened.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 736, "question": "The hologram thing is a rumor that's not true?", "qSentId": 735}, {"answer": "He started all that.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 745, "question": "You started all that?", "qSentId": 744}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120527pmt", "aSentId": 755, "question": "Can we bring you on the stage?", "qSentId": 754}]